Privacy Policy | Epsom College                              

 Search

 Search

Privacy Policy
==============

Who We Are
----------

Our website address is: https://www.epsomcollege.org.uk.

This policy explains how Epsom College collects and uses information via its website. Please click on the following links for more information on how the College uses information about pupils and parents.

For further information, to receive support or make a complaint relating to the College’s use of your personal data please contact our Bursar, Mr Paul Ratcliffe at [bursar@epsomcollege.org.uk](mailto:bursar@epsomcollege.org.uk)

Privacy Policy
--------------

(a) Epsom College is a co-educational independent school located in Epsom, Surrey, England, which provides both boarding and day school education for pupils between the ages of 11-18.

(b) Epsom College is a registered charity and its charity number is 312046-146.  It is a subsidiary charity of The Royal Medical Foundation Of Epsom College, whose charity number is 312046.

(c) Epsom College is also registered as a company in England and Wales under company number 04009200, and its registered office is at Epsom College, College Road, Epsom, Surrey, KT17 4JQ.

(d) ‘Epsom College’/’we’/’us’, for the purposes of this Privacy Policy, means both the registered charity and the registered company referred to above.

(e) The Site is a UK-based website and we take reasonable care to comply with the requirements of the UK Data Protection Act 1998 (**‘the Act’**) relating to the personal information you supply on the Site.

(f) For the purposes of the Act, the data controller is Epsom College and it is registered as a data controller with the Information Commissioner for the United Kingdom.

Comments
--------

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymised string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service Privacy Policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

Media
-----

If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

Cookies
-------

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt into saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you visit our login page, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

Embedded Content From Other Websites
------------------------------------

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

Who We Share Your Data With
---------------------------

If you request a password reset, your IP address will be included in the reset email.

How Long We Retain Your Data
----------------------------

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognise and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

What Rights You Have Over Your Data
-----------------------------------

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

Where Your Data Is Sent
-----------------------

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

### Where Next?

##### Quick links

##### Finding Epsom

Epsom College  
College Road  
Epsom, Surrey  
KT17 4JQ

##### Get in touch

##### Search our site

 Search

* © Copyright Epsom College 2024
* [Web design](https://www.thewebkitchen.co.uk/) by [TWK](https://www.thewebkitchen.co.uk/)
